scenicreflections.com 2015-05-19

# ScenicReflections Premium Free Desktop Screensaver Downloads

PRIVACY POLICY AND TERMS OF USE FOR  
SCENICREFLECTIONS.COM

PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy applies to the use of ScenicReflections.com.

We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site. 

Log Files and Cookies:  
This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you have submitted while on our site.

We, at various times, sometimes use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information,browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org .

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collectcertain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies orweb beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during yourvisit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websiteslikely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioraladvertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymousinformation, you can visit http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml 

Advertising and Analytics:  
This site uses Google Adwords and Analytics services. You can learn more about Google’s policies at the Google advertising policy site: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Registration And Use Of Personal Information:  
Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. However, this site may make forums, blogs, message boards or similar available to its users. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments or provide articles. 

If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

Please note that if you post comments or articles to any forum, blog or message board on this site, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels.

We also provide visitors to our website the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. In this case, we ask the visitor for his or her email address and name. These communications will include our regular newsletter, product promotions and any other information that we feel may be pertinent to the visitor. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by clicking on the the "unsubscribe" link in any email we send to you, or by contacting us here: http://www.scenicreflections.com/contactform.php

Again, if you provide us with your email address and/or name for the purposes of receiving communications from us, this information will not be shared with any third-party organization.

Access To Personally Identifiable Information:  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you may request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by contacting us here: http://www.scenicreflections.com/contactform.php

Security:  
We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore, as is the case with ANY organization - we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information. 

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by contacting us here: http://www.scenicreflections.com/contactform.php

Links to Other Websites:  
This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

Legal Disclaimer:  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

Contact Details:  
If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, or you wish to contact us by phone or postal mail, our contact information is as follows: 

Bit Wise Publishing, LLC  
PO Box 29  
Cumming, GA 30028  
678-513-0170

You can also contact us here:  http://www.scenicreflections.com/contactform.php

This privacy policy was last updated on March 10th, 2015
